We are all aware of climate change and how it is threatening our planet.
我们都深知气候变化的存在，也清楚它正威胁着我们的星球。
Industrialisation, our disposable culture and population growth are some of the reasons why we are seeing average temperatures rise and more extreme weather events.
工业化发展、一次性消费文化以及人口增长，都是导致全球平均气温上升、极端天气事件频发的部分原因。
And scientists are finding more evidence that the situation is getting worse.
而且科学家们还在不断发现新的证据，表明情况正在持续恶化。
The rise in global temperatures is the most important thing that experts analyse.
全球气温上升是专家们分析的重中之重。
They say keeping it below 1.5 centigrade will avoid the worst climate impacts.
他们表示，将气温升幅控制在1.5摄氏度以内，就能避免气候变化带来的最严重影响。
But The World Meteorological Organisation says there’s a 20% possibility the critical mark will be broken in any one year before 2024 – and there’s a 70% chance it will be broken in one or more months in those five years.
但世界气象组织指出，2024年之前的任意一年，气温升幅突破这一临界值的概率为20%；而在这五年期间，至少有一个月突破该临界值的概率高达70%。
This isn’t great news for the Arctic, where the impact will be greatest: warming by twice the global average this year.
这对北极地区而言绝非好消息，该地区受到的影响将最为严重：今年北极的升温速度是全球平均水平的两倍。
Temperatures in the Siberian Arctic reached record averages in June – one area reached more than 30℃.
六月，西伯利亚北极地区的平均气温创下历史新高，其中有一片区域的气温甚至超过了30摄氏度。
This heat helped to fan wildfires, which in turn released 59 million tonnes of carbon dioxide.
高温助长了野火的蔓延，这些野火转而释放出5900万吨二氧化碳。
Meanwhile, in Western Europe, experts predict over the next five years rising sea levels will cause more storms.
与此同时，专家预测未来五年内，西欧地区的海平面上升将引发更多风暴。
But these events should not surprise us.
但这些现象其实并不出人意料。
Professor Martin Siegert from Imperial College London told the BBC this is “in line with predictions of global warming going back decades now.
伦敦帝国理工学院的马丁·西格特教授向英国广播公司表示，这“与数十年前关于全球变暖的预测完全吻合。
We don’t really need further confirmation of this problem, but here it is anyway.”
我们其实并不需要更多证据来证实这个问题，但事实还是摆在了眼前。”
He thinks if you change the weather in the Arctic you are likely to see the effects ripple out around the world.
他认为，一旦北极的气候模式发生改变，其影响很可能会波及全球。
We know that carbon emissions from human activities is partly to blame for our warming planet, but it seems measures to reduce this are not having much effect.
我们都知道，人类活动产生的碳排放是地球变暖的部分原因，但目前来看，减排措施的效果并不明显。
The BBC’s Justin Rowlatt writing about the effects of events in the Arctic, says: “Climate scientists simply don’t know for certain what those effects are likely to be, but climate models suggest they will lead to more extreme weather events – heatwaves and severe storms.”
英国广播公司的贾斯汀·罗莱特在撰文分析北极地区气候变化的影响时指出：“气候科学家们尚无法确切判断这些影响具体会是什么，但气候模型显示，它们将引发更多极端天气事件——比如热浪和强风暴。”